<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="generic">
  <id>org.kde.development</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Joc de desenvolupament de programari del KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc de desenvolupament de programari de KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Εργαλειοθήκη ανάπτυξης KDE λογισμικού (SDK)</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kit de desarrollo de software de KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KDE arenduskomplekt</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDE Softwarea garatzeko tresna-multzoa</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Bibliothèque de développement de logiciels pour KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">केडीई सॉफ़टवेयर विकास के लिए उपकरण समूह</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Strumenti di sviluppo dei programmi di KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE 소프트웨어 개발 도구</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Zestaw do rozwoju oprogramowania KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kit de Desenvolvimento de Aplicações do KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE SDK</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Набор для разработки программного обеспечения KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE sada na vývoj softvéru</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDE Software Development Kit</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE Programvaruutvecklingsmiljö</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KDE Yazılım Geliştirme Takımı</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Набір для розробки програмного забезпечення KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Software Development Kitxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE 软件开发套件</name>
  <icon type="remote">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdesdk-devenv-dependencies/applications-development.svg</icon>
  <summary>A full SDK for developing Qt and KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Un SDK complet per a desenvolupar aplicacions Qt i KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Un SDK complet per a desenvolupar aplicacions Qt i KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Ein vollständiges SDK für die Entwicklung von Qt und KDE-Anwendungen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Ένα πλήρες SDK για την ανάπτυξη Qt και KDE εφαρμογών</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">A full SDK for developing Qt and KDE Applications</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Un completo SDK para desarrollar aplicaciones de Qt y de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Qt eta KDE aplikazioak garatzeko SDK oso bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une bibliothèque complète pour le développement d'applications Qt et KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">क्यूट एवं केडीई के अनुप्रयोगों के विकास के लिए उपकरण समूह</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Sebuah SDK lengkap untuk mengembangkan Aplikasi Qt dan KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Una SDK completa per sviluppare applicazioni Qt e KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Qt와 KDE 프로그램을 개발할 수 있는 완전한 SDK</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een volledige SDK voor ontwikkeling van Qt en KDE toepassingen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Full SDK for utvikling av Qt- og KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Pełny SDK do rozwoju programów Qt oraz KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Um SDK completo para desenvolver aplicações para o Qt e o KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Um kit de desenvolvimento de software (SDK) completo para desenvolver aplicativos Qt e KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Полный набор для разработки ПО на основе Qt и приложений KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Plné SDK na vývoj Qt a KDE aplikácií</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Popoln komplet za razvoj programske opreme za aplikacij Qt in KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En fullständig programvaruutvecklingsmiljö för utveckling av Qt- och KDE-program</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Qt ve KDE uygulamaları geliştirmek için tam bir Yazılım Geliştirme Takımı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Повний набір для розробки програмного забезпечення на основі Qt і програм KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxA full SDK for developing Qt and KDE Applicationsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This is the KDE SDK: everything you need for developing Qt-based KDE software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquest és el SDK del KDE: tot el que cal per a desenvolupar programari KDE basat en les Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Este és el SDK de KDE: tot el que cal per a desenvolupar programari KDE basat en les Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dies ist das KDE-SDK (Software Development Kit): Alles was Sie zur Entwicklung von KDE-Software auf der Basis der Qt-Bibliotheken benötigen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτό είναι το SDK του KDE: ό,τι χρειάζεστε για να αναπτύξετε KDE λογισμικό με βάση την Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This is the KDE SDK: everything you need for developing Qt-based KDE software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Esto es KDE SDK: todo lo que necesita para desarrollar software de KDE basado en Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KDE SDK da hau: Qt oinarriko KDE softwarea garatzeko behar duzun guztia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ceci est une bibliothèque KDE, tout ce dont vous avez besoin pour le développement de logiciels KDE utilisant Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">यह केडीई सॉफ़टवेयर विकास उपकरण समूह है: क्यूट आधारित केडीई सॉफ़टवेयर के विकास के लिए ज़रूरतमन्द है</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini adalah KDE SDK: semua yang kamu butuhkan untuk mengembangkan perangkat lunak KDE berbasis Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questa è una SDK di KDE: tutto quello che ti può servire per sviluppare programmi di KDE basati su Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE SDK입니다: Qt 기반 KDE 소프트웨어를 개발할 때 필요한 모든 도구입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Dit is de KDE SDK: alles wat u nodig hebt voor ontwikkeling van op Qt gebaseerde KDE software.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Dette er KDE-SDK-en: Alt du treng for å utvikla Qt-baserte KDE-program.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Oto KDE SDK: wszystko czego potrzebujesz do rozwoju oprogramowania KDE opartego na Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Este é o SDK do KDE: tudo o que precisa para desenvolver aplicações para o KDE baseadas no Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Este é o KDE SDK: tudo que você precisa para desenvolver softwares KDE baseado em Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Это набор библиотек для разработки программного обеспечения KDE: всё, что вам понадобится для разработки основанных на Qt программ KDE.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">To je komplet za razvoj programske opreme KDE; vse kar potrebujete za razvoj aplikacij s Qt za programe KDE</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det här är KDE:s Programvaruutvecklingsmiljö: allt du behöver för att utveckla Qt-baserad KDE-programvara.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bu, KDE Yazılm Geliştirme Takımıdır: Qt tabanlı KDE yazılımları geliştirmek için gereksinim duyduğunuz her şey.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Це набір бібліотек для розробки програмного забезпечення KDE: усе, що вам знадобиться для розробки програмного забезпечення KDE на основі Qt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis is the KDE SDK: everything you need for developing Qt-based KDE software.xx</p>
    <p>It will install the required dependencies for compiling most KDE software (Frameworks, Applications, and Plasma). It will also offer to install tools that make KDE development easy, including the KDevelop IDE, Kate text editor, and Cuttlefish icon viewer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Instal·larà les dependències requerides per a compilar la majoria del programari KDE (Frameworks, aplicacions i Plasma). També oferirà la instal·lació d'eines que faciliten el desenvolupament del KDE, incloent-hi l'IDE KDevelop, l'editor de text Kate i el visor d'icones Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Instal·larà les dependències requerides per a compilar la majoria del programari KDE (Frameworks, aplicacions i Plasma). També oferirà la instal·lació d'eines que faciliten el desenvolupament de KDE, incloent-hi l'IDE KDevelop, l'editor de text Kate i el visor d'icones Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Es installiert alle notwendigen Abhängigkeiten für das Kompilieren von KDE-Software wie Frameworks, Anwendungen and Plasma. Damit können Sie auch Hilfsprogramme wie die integrierte Entwicklungsumgebung KDevelop, den Texteditor Kate und Cuttlefish zur Anzeige von Symbolen installieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Θα εγκαταστήσει τις απαραίτητες εξαρτήσεις για τη μεταγλώττιση του μεγαλύτερου μέρους του λογισμικού του KDE (Frameworks, Εφαρμογές και Plasma). Θα προτείνει επίσης την εγκατάσταση εργαλείων που θα διευκολύνουν την ανάπτυξη του KDE μαζί και του KDevelp IDE, τον κειμενογράφου Kate και του προγράμματος προβολής εικονιδίων Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It will install the required dependencies for compiling most KDE software (Frameworks, Applications, and Plasma). It will also offer to install tools that make KDE development easy, including the KDevelop IDE, Kate text editor, and Cuttlefish icon viewer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Instalará las dependencias necesarias para compilar la mayor parte del software de KDE (Frameworks, aplicaciones y Plasma). También ofrecerá la posibilidad de instalar herramientas para facilitar el desarrollo de KDE, incluyendo el IDE KDevelop, el editor de texto Kate y el visor de iconos Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KDE software gehiena konpilatzeko behar diren mendekotasunak (Frameworks, Aplikazioak, eta Plasma) instalatuko ditu. KDE garapena errazten duten tresnak ere instalatuko ditu, KDevelop IDEa, Kate testu editorea, eta Cuttlefish ikono erakuslea barne.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ceci installera les dépendances nécessaires pour la compilation de la plupart des logiciels de KDE (Atelier, applications et Plasma). Il vous offrira aussi d'installer des outils pour rendre les développement sous KDE faciles, en incluant l'environnement de développement KDevelop, l'éditeur de texte Kate et l'afficheur d'icônes Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">यह केडीई सॉफ़टवेयर (फ्रेमवर्क्स, अनुप्रयोग, प्लाज़मा) को कम्पाईल करने के लिए डिपेन्डेन्सीस स्थापित करेगा। यह केडीई के विकास को और आसान बनाने के लिए अतिरिक्त अनुप्रयोगों को स्थापित करने का सुझाव देगा, जैसे की, केडेवेलेप आइडीई, केट पाठ संपादक, और कटलफ़िश प्रतीक प्रदर्शक।</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ini akan menginstal dependensi yang diperlukan untuk mengkompilasi sebagian besar perangkat lunak KDE (Frameworks, Applications, dan Plasma). Ia juga akan menawarkan untuk menginstal alat yang membuat pengembangan KDE lebih mudah, termasuk KDevelop IDE, editor teks Kate, dan penampil ikon Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Installerà le dipendenze richieste per la compilazione della maggior parte dei programmi di KDE (Frameworks, Applications e Plasma). Offrirà anche la possibilità di installare strumenti che semplificano lo sviluppo di KDE, tra cui l'IDE di KDevelop, l'editor di testo di Kate e il visualizzatore di icone di Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">대부분의 KDE 소프트웨어(프레임워크, 프로그램, Plasma)를 컴파일할 때 필요한 의존성을 설치합니다. KDE 개발을 쉽게 도와 줄 수 있는 도구인 KDevelop IDE, Kate 텍스트 편집기, Cuttlefish 아이콘 뷰어를 설치합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het zal de vereiste afhankelijkheden voor compileren van de meeste KDE software (Frameworks, Applications en Plasma) installeren. Het zal ook het installeren van hulpmiddelen bieden die ontwikkelen in KDE gemakkelijk maakt, inclusief de KDevelop IDE, Kate tekstbewerker en de Cuttlefish pictogramviewer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Han vil installera dei nødvendige avhengnadane for kompilering av dei fleste KDE-programma (Frameworks, Applications og Plasma). Han vil òg tilby å installera verktøy som gjev KDE-utvikling lettare, inkludert IDE-en KDevelop, skrive­programmet Kate og ikon­visaren Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wgra wymagane zależności do skompilowania większości programów KDE (Szkielety, Aplikacje oraz Plazma). Da także możliwość wgrania narzędzi, czyniących rozwój KDE łatwiejszym, a wśród nich IDE KDevelop, edytor tekstu Kate oraz przeglądarkę ikon Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Ele irá instalar as dependências necessárias para compilar a maioria das aplicações do KDE (Plataformas, Aplicações e o Plasma). Também irá oferecer a possibilidade de instalar as ferramentas que facilitam o desenvolvimento no KDE, incluindo o IDE KDevelop, o editor de texto Kate e o visualizador de ícones Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Ele irá instalar todas as dependências necessárias para compilar a maioria dos softwares KDE (Frameworks, Applications e Plasma). Também irá oferecer instalar ferramentas que tornam fácil o desenvolvimento do KDE, incluindo a IDE KDevelop, o editor de textos Kate e o visualizador de ícones Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Будут установлены необходимые зависимости для сборки большинства программ KDE (библиотек, приложений и Plasma). Также будет предложена установка инструментов, облегчающих разработку для KDE, включая среду разработки KDevelop, текстовый редактор Kate и средство просмотра иконок Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Namestil bo vsa potrebna orodja za prevajanje večine programske opreme KDE(Frameworks, Applications, and Plasma)). Ponudil bo tudi namestitev orodij ki olajšajo razvoj KDE, vključno z razvojnim okoljem KDevelop, urejevalnikom besedil Kate in pregledovalnikom ikon Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det installerar nödvändiga beroenden för att kompilera det mesta av KDE:s programvara (Ramverk, Program, och Plasma). Det erbjuder också att installera verktyg som gör KDE-utveckling enkel, inklusive den integrerad utvecklingsmiljön KDevelop, texteditorn Kate, och ikonvisningsverktyget Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Çoğu KDE yazılımını derlemek için gereken bağımlılıkları kurar (Kod Kitaplıkları, Uygulamalar ve Plasma). Ayrıca KDE geliştirmesini kolaylaştıran diğer araçları da kurmayı önerir; örneğin, KDevelop Tümleşik Geliştirme Ortamı, Kate metin düzenleyicisi ve Cuttlefish simge görüntüleyici.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Буде встановлено усі потрібні залежності для збирання більшості програмного забезпечення KDE (бібліотек, програм і Плазми). Також буде запропоновано встановити інструменти, які полегшують розробку KDE, зокрема комплексне середовище для розробки KDevelop, текстовий редактор Kate та програму для перегляду піктограм Cuttlefish.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt will install the required dependencies for compiling most KDE software (Frameworks, Applications, and Plasma). It will also offer to install tools that make KDE development easy, including the KDevelop IDE, Kate text editor, and Cuttlefish icon viewer.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdesdk-devenv-dependencies/kdevelop5-breeze_2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kdesdk-devenv-dependencies/cuttlefish.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <suggests>
    <id>org.kde.kate.desktop</id>
    <id>org.kde.kdevelop.desktop</id>
    <id>org.kde.plasma.themeexplorer.desktop</id>
    <id>org.kde.plasma.lookandfeelexplorer.desktop</id>
  </suggests>
  <url type="help">https://techbase.kde.org/Development/Tutorials</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
