<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.activityworkshop.gpsprune</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">gpsprune.desktop</launchable>
  <name>GpsPrune</name>
  <summary>Visualize, edit and prune GPS tracks</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>GpsPrune is an application for viewing, editing and converting coordinate data from GPS systems. Basically it's a tool to let you play with your GPS data after you get home from your trip.</p>
    <p>It can load data from arbitrary text-based formats (for example, any tab-separated or comma-separated file) or Xml, or directly from a GPS receiver. It can display the data (as map view using openstreetmap images and as altitude profile), edit this data (for example delete points and ranges, sort waypoints, compress tracks), and save the data (in various text-based formats). It can also export data as a Gpx file, or as Kml/Kmz for import into Google Earth, or send it to a GPS receiver.</p>
    <p>Some example uses of GpsPrune include cleaning up tracks by deleting wayward points - either recorded by error or by unintended detours. It can also be used to compare and combine tracks, convert to and from various formats, compress tracks, export data to Google Earth, or to analyse data to calculate distances, altitudes and so on.</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://activityworkshop.net/software/gpsprune/screengrabs/gpsprune_13_ordnance_survey.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://activityworkshop.net/software/gpsprune/screengrabs/gpsprune_13_hungarian.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://activityworkshop.net/software/gpsprune/screengrabs/prune_12_ubuntu.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/activityworkshop/GpsPrune/issues</url>
  <url type="homepage">https://activityworkshop.net/software/gpsprune/</url>
</component>
